{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Type?",
      "answer": "LSTM"
    },
    {
      "question": "Function?",
      "answer": "Sigma"
    },
    {
      "question": "Activation?",
      "answer": "Tanh"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gate?",
      "answer": "Forget"
    },
    {
      "question": "Memory?",
      "answer": "Cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "Equation?",
      "answer": "Input"
    },
    {
      "question": "Weight?",
      "answer": "W"
    },
    {
      "question": "Matrix?",
      "answer": "U"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cell?",
      "answer": "Ct"
    },
    {
      "question": "Output?",
      "answer": "ht"
    }
  ]
}